bikeclothingmall.com 2016-11-09

# Privacy Policy | Bike Clothing Mall

BikeClothingMall takes your privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes what personal information we collect and how we use it.

Routine Information Collection All web servers track basic information about their visitors. This information includes, but is not limited to, IP addresses, browser details, timestamps and referring pages. None of this information can personally identify specific visitors to this site. The information is tracked for routine administration and maintenance purposes.

Cookies and Web Beacons Where necessary, BikeClothingMall uses cookies to store information about a visitor’s preferences and history in order to better serve the visitor and/or present the visitor with customized content.

Advertising partners and other third parties may also use cookies, scripts and/or web beacons to track visitors to our site in order to display advertisements and other useful information. Such tracking is done directly by the third parties through their own servers and is subject to their own privacy policies.

Controlling Your Privacy Note that you can change your browser settings to disable cookies if you have privacy concerns. Disabling cookies for all sites is not recommended as it may interfere with your use of some sites. The best option is to disable or enable cookies on a per-site basis. Consult your browser documentation for instructions on how to block cookies and other tracking mechanisms.

Special Note About Google Advertising This site may carry interest based advertising for which Google or other third party vendors use cookies to serve advertisements on this site.Googles use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our visitors based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie at any time by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html.

Contact Information Concerns or questions about this privacy policy can be directed to info@ BikeClothingMall .com for further clarification.
